In this clip we're going to talk about what Bill my mechanic is doing.
He's changing torsion arms, because last night we had a bar go bad.
Bars get twisted one way, and you can only drive them one way so they twist with the track, with the way the car is twisting.
And if you put them in backwards, it ruins the bar, and the bar goes bad and you kind of just, you know, it just gets saggy.
So he's just changing it up to make sure that it's all going to run good today.
You know, you put the torsion bars on to get an angle on the axle.
In the last session it just wouldn't stick to the track and that's you know, one of the reasons that we are changing this, is because a bar went bad, it just you know made the whole set up just kind of went bad with the bar.
Bill is very important to me.
He's my right hand man, right?
Oh yeah.
But now he's on my left side.
Anyways, actually I couldn't do this without them.
There is no way I could be here by myself.
You know, I have so many people supporting me.
You know, Ginns Racing, you know they bring the car here, they keep it at their house and their shop and Bill works on it and they work really really hard.
And they're great people to be around.
And they put everything towards our racing to try to get me where I need to be at, in Nascar some day.
So.